Simon Flexner Papers 1891-1946 Mss.B.F365
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Simon Flexner Papers, 1891-1946; 115.5 linear feet
  - Hale, George Ellery, 1915-1939; 5 folders
    Includes: Correspondence about vivisection debate in California, 1915-17. Correspondence about SF as chairman of Medical Division, National Research Council, 1918, and choice of men to serve on its Executive Board. Copy of a letter from H. D. Dakin to Hale about a suggestion of Royal Society of London that NRC form a food committee similar to that of Royal Society, 1/19/18. Correspondence about war organization of NAS Council members and members of Executive Committee of NRC. Correspondence on SF's attending a meeting at Royal Society of London as delegate of NAS to discuss formation of an interallied research council, Oct. 1918. Copy of a letter from Hale to W. W. Keen on outlines for Tnternational Research Council, 5/28/19. Correspondence on death of Bumstead, 1921, and the appointment of his successor as chairman of NBC. SF feels a man from the physico-chemical sciences should be appointed. Letter from Hale to SF explaining reasons for resigning from NRC Fellowship Board in Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics. He feels, with removal of Millikan to California, there should not be three people on the board from the same institution, 10/3/21. Correspondence about Hale's 200" telescope, 1930-1931. Correspondence on proposed donation by Mrs. Kerckhoff of an institution in memory of her husband. Both Hale and SF feel the money should be given to T. H. Morgan's laboratory to develop the work there in biophysics and biochemistry, Aug. 1921. Further correspondence concerning International Research Council, also mention of plans put forward to Rockefeller Foundation to promote research in physics and chemistry, 7/17/18. Letter to SF about Einstein's proposed visit to U.S., 3/4/21. (folders not fully organized)
  - Hale, William E.
  - Hale, William J.
  - Hale, Worth
  - Hall, A. D.
  - Hall, Andy
  - Hall, Arthur J.
  - Hall, Bolton
  - Hall, C. H.
  - Hall, Edwin H.
  - Hall, Frederick A.
  - Hall, G. B.
  - Hall, H. B.
  - Hall, Ivan C.
  - Hall, J. Walker
  - Hall, R. C.
  - Hall, Robert A.
    - Research in Pathology and Medicine
  - Hallauer, C.
  - Hallberg, J. H.
  - Halle, Hiram J.
  - Haller, Herbert L. J.
  - Halley, Charles R. L.
  - Halliburton, William Dobinson, 1916-1917; 3 items
  - Halliday, C. H.
  - Hallos, Joseph
  - Halloway, Miss
  - Halloway, W. A.
  - Hallquist, Herman
  - Hallsey, Ednah B.
  - Halsey, Mrs. Charles B.
  - Halsey, J. T.
  - Halsey, L. M.
  - Halsey, R. T. H.
  - Halsey, Stewart and Co.
  - Halsted, Elenore
  - Halstead, Nell E.
  - Halsted, William S., 2 folders
  - Halton, Joseph
  - Hamann, C. A.
  - Hamburger, Carl
  - Hamburger, Franz
  - Hamburger, Hartog Jakob, 1919-1923; 12 items
    Includes: Hamburger thanks SF for hospitality during his visit to RIMR 1922 and is of opinion such an institute should be established in Groningen.
  - Hamburger, Louis P.
  - Hamburger, Walter W.
  - Hamel, Dr.
  - Hamill, R. C.
  - Hamill, Samuel McClintock
  - Hamilton, Alice
  - Hamilton, Annie Lee
  - Hamilton, Charles M.
  - Hamilton, Fleming
  - Hamilton, Gertrude
  - Hamilton, Herbert J.
  - Hamilton, James
  - Hamilton, John A.
  - Hamilton, Juliet P.
  - Hamilton, Maylin
  - Hamilton, Richard T.
  - Hamilton, Theodosia S.
  - Hamilton, Thomas W.
  - Hamilton, W. F.
  - Hamilton, Iselin and Co.
  - Hamlin, Fred E.
  - Hamlin, George D.
  - Hamman, Louis
  - Hammarstein, Einar, 1922; 1 item
    Includes: Introduction from SF to Hammarstein of Abraham Flexner.
  - Hammel, Carolyn
  - Hammer, David
  - Hammes, E. M.
  - Hammett, Frederick S.
  - Hammond, C. S. and Co.
  - Hammond, Donald
  - Hammond, Emily
  - Hammond, Graeme
  - Hamond, Roland
  - Hamot Hospital
  - Hampton, G. G.
  - Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute
  - Hampton's Magazine
  - Hanan, James T.
  - Hanauer, S. S.
  - Hanawalt, D.
  - Hance, Irwin H.
  - Hance, Robert T.
  - Hancock, M. W.
  - Hand, Alfred
  - Hand, Claudius A.
  - Hand, Frances
  - Hand, Learned
  - Handick, Harry F.
  - Handley, W. Sampson
  - Handy, Dora Keen
  - Handy, Margaret
  - Hanelius, William
  - Hanes, Frederic M.
  - Haney, Joseph A.
  - Hanford, A. C.
  - Hanford, H. B.
  - Hanford, John H
  - Hanford, John M.
  - Hanft Bros.
  - Hanger, Franklin M.
  - Hanks, John T
  - Hanley, George
  - Hanna, J. B.
  - Hanna, Paul R.
  - Hanna, W. J.
  - Hannah, Louis
  - Hanner, Lt. Col.
  - Hanner, J. W.
  - Hannon, Robert R.
  - Hanotaux, Gabriel
  - Hanrahan, John J.
  - Hansell, Howard F.
  - Hanselman, Louis
  - Hansen, Anna D.
  - Hansen, Henry C.
  - Hansman, G. H.
  - Hanson, Adolph M.
  - Hanson, Ernest
  - Hanson, Frank Blair, 1936; 2 items
    Includes: Request for SF's opinions of Dr. E. Uhlenhuth.
  - Hanson, J. E.
  - Hanus, Paul H.
  - Hapgood, Charles H.
  - Hapgood, Hutchins
  - Hapgood, Norman
  - Happe, F. A.
  - Happy Hills Convalescent Home
  - Harbitz, Francis
  - Harbord, James G.
  - Harcourt, Brace and Co.
  - Harcourt, Lewis
  - Hardenbergh, Mr.
  - Hardenbergh, J. W.
  - Hardenbergh, W. A.
  - Hardgrove, George W.
  - Harding, Esther
  - Harding, H. A.
  - Harding, J. J.
  - Hardy, Mary
  - Hare, Hobart A.
  - Hare, Robert A.
  - Hargreaves, H. Stanley
  - Harkavy, E. Edward
  - Harkavy, Joseph
  - Harkey, Tula Lake
  - Harkness, Edward S.
  - Harlan, Henry D.
  - Harnack, Dr. Von
  - Harned, F. P.
  - Harned, R. W.
  - Harnett, Charles A.
  - Harper, C. A.
  - Harper, Clarence
  - Harper, J. E.
  - Harper, Robert A.
  - Harper and Brothers
  - Harper's Magazine
  - Harpole, W. S.
  - Harrell, Lillian S.
  - Harrelson, A. M.
  - Harriman, Karl Edwin
  - Harriman Laboratory
  - Harrington, Carrie B.
  - Harrington, F. B.
  - Harrington, John W.
  - Harris, A. W.
  - Harris, D. L.
  - Harris, E. Eliot
  - Harris, Fraser
  - Harris, H. A.
  - Harris, H. L.
  - Harris, Harriette
  - Harris, J.
  - Harris, Louis I.
  - Harris, Norman McC.
  - Harris, Norman MacL.
  - Harris, Paul N.
  - Harris, R. J.
  - Harris, Seale
  - Harris, Thomas J.
  - Harris, W. J.
  - Harris, W. W.
  - Harris, William H.
  - Harris and Ewing
  - Harris Laboratories
  - Harrisburg Hospital
  - Harrison, Carlos
  - Harrison, Henry B.
  - Harrison, M.
  - Harrison, Ross Granville, 1910-1944; 35 items
    Includes: Introduction to SF for Dr. Rhoda Erdmann, 1911. Correspondence on Burrows' experiments with chick embryos, and Harrison's share of credit. Request to nominate Reinhard Dohrn for Nobel Prize, 1928. Correspondence about an antivivisectionist suit against Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn, 1944.
  - Harrison, Shelby M.
  - Harrop, George A., 1923; 5 items
    Includes: Correspondence about supply of cerebrospinal fluid to RIMR. Correspondence about work in insulin therapy classes at Columbia University-Presbyterian Hospital, 1923.
  - Harrow, Benjamin
  - Hart, Mrs. Boises C.
  - Hart, Charles D.
  - Hart, E. B.
  - Hart, Hastings H.
  - Hart, T. Stuart
  - Hart, William Morris
  - Hartfiel, Thomas C.
  - Hartfield, Joseph M.
  - Hartford, Courant
  - Hartley, Percivil
  - Hartman, Carl G.
  - Hartman, Gustave
  - Hartman, H. A.
  - Hartman, Henry
  - Hartman, Mrs. John
  - Hartswitz, T. M.
  - Hartung, Paul Verlag
  - Hartung, Pauline
  - Hartwell, John A.
  - Hartzell, M. B.
  - Harvard
    - Harvard Alumni Ass'n
    - Harvard, Alumni Bulletin
    - Harvard Athletic Ass'tn
    - Harvard Club of N.Y.C.
    - Harvard College
    - Harvard College Library
    - Harvard Cooperative Society, Inc.
    - Harvard Faculty Club
    - Harvard Fund Council
    - Harvard University
    - Harvard University Bussey Institution
    - Harvard University Medical School Curriculum
    - Harvard University Quinqeunnial Catalogue
    - Harvard War Records
  - Harvey, E. L.
  - Harvey, H. R.
  - Harvey, Henry T.
  - Harvey Society
  - Harvie, John B.
  - Harwood, George
  - Haselbauer, Peter P., 4 folders
    Includes: Correspondence about his work with meningitis serum on rabbits; charts and daily reports. Reports on his work with herpes and encephalitis.
    - Folder 1, 1937
    - Folder 2, 1922-1931
    - Folder 3, 1932-1938
    - Misc. Polio. Data
  - Hasenjaeger, Ella
  - Hashiba, G. K.
  - Haskell, C. N.
  - Haskell, Henry S.
  - Haskell, J.
  - Haskell, Juliana
  - Haskin, Frederic J.
  - Haskin, William H.
  - Hasking, Artbur P.
  - Haslett, M. E.
  - Hassa, Mahdi
  - Hassin, George B.
  - Hassman, David M.
  - Hast, Lisette
  - Hasting, George A.
  - Hastings, Albert Baird, 1926-1931; 10 items
  - Hastings, Claire W.
  - Hastings, Gordon
  - Hata, S.
  - Hatchards
  - Hatcher, Robert A.
  - Hatfield, Charles J., 3 folders
    Includes: Correspondence concerning Advisory Council meetings of Henry Phipps Institute; report to Council May 1916, March 1918 and Feb. 1926, Correspondence about SF's taking chairmanship of the National Tuberculosis Association.
    - Folder 1, 1914-1917
    - Folder 2, 1918-1924
    - Folder 3, 1925-1936
  - Hatfield, John N.
  - Hatmaker, James R.
  - Hatton, T. Chalkley
  - Hauben, S. S.
  - Hauer, Alexandre
  - Haulenbeek, Mr.
  - Hauptman, Kenneth B.
  - Hauser, Bertram J.
  - Hauser, G. H.
  - Hausheer, Walter C.
  - Hausman, W. A., Jr.
  - Hausser, Karl Wilhelm
  - Haua, Adrian
  - Haven, A. P.
  - Haven, Samuel C.
  - Haven Country Club
  - Havens, James D.
  - Havens, Leon C.
  - Haverhill (Mass.), Board of Health
  - Haviland, C. Floyd
  - Hawk, Charles Lyle
  - Hawk, Philip B.
  - Hawkes, Charles E.
  - Hawkins, F. H.
  - Hawkins, James A.
  - Hawkins, R. R.
  - Hawks-Potts, F. L.
  - Hawksley and Sons
  - Hawley, George W.
  - Haworth, E. B.
  - Haws, Mary E.
  - Hay, Isaac Minis
  - Hay, William W.
  - Hayashi, H.
  - Hayden, Charles
  - Hayden, F. L.
  - Haye, Helen
  - Hayeben, Clark
  - Hayek, F. M.
  - Hayes, Clara Edna
  - Hayes, J. D.
  - Hayes Storage, Packing and Removal Service
  - Hayes, Wilhelmina C.
  - Hayford, Arnold D.
  - Hayford, Lawrence D.
  - Haynes, Royal Storrs
  - Hays, Charles E.
  - Hays, Elma Wood
  - Hays, Harold
  - Hays, I. Minis
  - Hays, Will H.
  - Haythorn, Samuel R..
  - Hayward, Walter B.
  - Hazard, Mildred Owen
  - Hazell, Joseph W.
  - Hazen, C. M.
  - Hazen, Tracy E.
  - Head, Benjamin L.
  - Head, Henry
  - Head, Sir Henry
  - Headlee, T. J.
  - Heagle, William
  - Heald, A. A.
  - Heald, F. D.
  - Healy, Horace
  - Healy, William P.
  - Hean, Clarence S.
  - Heaney, Norman S.
  - Heany, J. A.
  - Heard, George P.
  - Hearsts International
  - Heasty, Robert G.
  - Heath, Sir Frank
  - Heath, H. Frank
  - Heath, Wilfrid Paul
  - Hebert, C. C.
  - Hebrew Orphan Asylum (New York, N.Y.)
  - Hebrew University
  - Hecht, Otto
  - Hecht, Selig, 1924; 1934; 8 items; 1 item
    Includes: Correspondence about his lecture to RIMR, 1924. Letters about a grant from International Education Board to study at Woods Hole, 1924.
  - Hedblom, Carl W.
  - Hedenbeu, James W.
  - Hedge, Mabel L.
  - Hedges, B. van D.
  - Hedinger, Ernst
  - Hedrick, A. W.
  - Hedrick, Mabel
  - Heger, F.
  - Heger, Ferdinand
  - Héger, Paul
  - Hegler, C.
  - Hegner, Robert W.
  - Heicher, M. K. W.
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 2 folders
    Includes: General correspondence about RIMR staff. Correspondence about his visit to Europe, 1924.
    - Folder 1, 1913-1923
    - Folder 2, 1924-1934; 1941-1942
  - Heidrick, Charles F.
  - Heifetz, Harold
  - Heim, Ludwig
  - Heiman, Henry
  - Heimann, Max
  - Heimrich, Joseph J.
  - Heimrod, George W.
  - Heinberg, C. J. S.
  - Heinberg, Carrie Bloom
  - Heins, Mrs. Walker D.
  - Heinze, Gustav
  - Heise, Frederick H.
  - Heise, Karl
  - Heiser, Victor G., 3 folders
    Includes: General correspondence about various projects funded by International Education Board. Many letters were originally attached to reports from commissions throughout the world. Correspondence concerning Red Cross Commission on rural sanitation in Poland, 1919; Yellow Fever Commission in Texas; and Hookworm Commission in Mexico.
    - Folder 1, 1916-1919
    - Folder 2, 1920
    - Folder 3, 1921-1934
  - Heisler, John C.
  - Heiss, H. E.
  - Heist, George D.
  - Hektoen, Ludvig, 2 folders
    Includes: Report of Committee on Scientific Research to House of Delegates, AMA, 1913-14. Correspondence about supplies of antimeningitis serum and infected spinal membranes. Correspondence on SF's acceptance of chairmanship of American Society for Microbiology, 1928. Letters about election of members to NAS, 1931; lists of nominees with votes received by each. Correspondence about election of a chairman of Division of Pathology and Bacteriology, NAS, 1932. Correspondence on establishing John F. Carty Medal for advancement of science, 1934. Correspondence about Advisory Committee on Fellowships of NRC. Correspondence about revisions of administration of NRC pobtdoctoral fellowships in physical and biological sciences, 1937.
    - Folder 1, 1913-1931
    - Folder 2, 1932-1937; 1943
  - Held, William
  - Helder, J.
  - Hellberg, S.
  - Hellendahl, Hugo
  - Heller, Jennifer
  - Heller, Julius S.
  - Hellfeld, E.
  - Hellman, Alfred M.
  - Hellman, George S.
  - Hellman, J. B.
  - Helme, F.
  - Helmholtz, Henry F.
  - Helmuth, William Tod
  - Hemingway, Alys G.
  - Hemmeter, John Conrad
  - Hemphill, C. R.
  - Hempl, George
  - Henderson, B. M.
  - Henderson, Charles J. M.
  - Henderson, Sir David
  - Henderson, Mrs. E. C.
  - Henderson, Mrs. J. H.
  - Henderson, Lawrence Joseph, 1922-1937; 15 items
    Includes: Letter from Henderson about his proposing George H. Whipple to NAS for work on secondary anemia, 4/26/29. Copy of a letter from Edwin Cohn to David Edsall on origins of Minot's work on anemia. Correspondence on election of Thorvald Madsen as a foreign member of NAS.
  - Henderson, V. E.
  - Henderson, W. F.
  - Henderson, Yandell, 1916-1943; 22 items
    Includes: Correspondence on his views on government regulations and government consultantships. Letters from Henderson asking SF's support for a change in Secretary of War's order prohibiting use of pound dogs for experimentation with poisonous gases, 1929. Correspondence, printed circulars etc. concerning annual meeting of NAS, 1931.
  - Hendrick, Arthur C.
  - Hendrick, Burton J.
  - Hendrick, Ellwood
  - Hendricks, E. B.
  - Henkes, Amelia L.
  - Henle, Mrs. Fred
  - Henle, James
  - Henman, Henry
  - Henmeter, John C.
  - Hennard, C. P.
  - Hennessey, Margaret M.
  - Hennessey, R. A.
  - Henning, Mrs. S. T.
  - Henri, Pauline
  - Henrici, Arthur T.
  - Henricsson, Erik
  - Henriques, Joaquim
  - Henry, Lady
  - Henry, Herbert
  - Henry, J. Norman, 2 folders
  - Henry Phipps Institute, 1919, 1921; 4 items
    Includes: Minutes of Advisory Council of Phipps Institute, June 1919, May 1921.
  - Henry Street Visiting Nurse Service
  - Henschen, Folke
  - Henschen, Salomon Eberhard
  - Hensley, W. J.
  - Henson, John G.
  - Hentel, Celia
  - Henze, Henry R.
  - Herada, K.
  - Herald, The
  - H. L. Herbert and Co.
  - Herbert and Huesgen Co.
  - Herbst, Curt
  - Herchmer, Mrs. Jean
  - Hercus, Charles E.
  - Herder, S.
  - Hering, Oswald C.
  - Heritage Press
  - Herm, Charles F.
  - Herman, David S.
  - Herman, I.
  - Herman, V.
  - Hermann, Mrs. M. C.
  - Hernandez, José A.
  - Herrick, Charles Judson, 1918; 2 items
  - Herrick, Frederick C.
  - Herrick, James B.
  - Herrick, Joseph C.
  - Herrick, Myron T.
  - Herrick, W. W.
  - Herrick, Walter R.
  - Herrick, William W.
  - Herring, Arthur P.
  - Herringham, Sir Wilmot
  - Herrman, Charles
  - Herron, F. L.
  - Hersch, T. Frank
  - Hersey, Harold W.
  - Hersey, Rex B.
  - Hershey, A. H.
  - Herter, Adele
  - Herter, Albert
  - Herter, Christian Archibald, 3 items
    Includes: Letter on the ultimate cost of construction of Rockefeller Institute Hospital.
  - Herter, Christine
  - Herter Lecturer
  - Hertig, Marshall
  - Herty, Charles H.
  - Hervey, Clifford R.
  - Hervey, O. B.
  - Herwarth, Edward
  - Herz, Jac
  - Herzog, Maximilian
  - Herzog, O.
  - Herzstein, Joseph
  - Hess, Alfred F.
  - Hess, George H.
  - Hess, Mrs. George H., Jr.
  - Hess, J. L.
  - Hess, L. R.
  - Hess, Sara Straus
  - Hess and Hess
  - Hessler, Robert
  - Hetherwood, Helen
  - Hetrick, Bernard D.
  - Hett, J. E.
  - Heuer, George J.
  - Heues, Edwin, Jr.
  - Heuser, J. Henry
  - Heusinkveld, Emily E.
  - Heuibach, Carl
  - Hewer, T. F.
  - Hewetson, S. W.
  - Hewlett, Albion Walter
  - Hewitt, D. W.
  - Heyd, Charles Gordon
  - Heydt, Charles O.
  - Heylunn, Elizabeth C.
  - Heymann, Bruno
  - Heymann, Franziska
  - Heymann, Karl
  - Heymans, J. F.
  - Hibbard, C.
  - Hibben, John G.
  - Hibbert, Dr.
  - Hibbs, Russell A.
  - Hickling, D. Percy
  - Hickman, C. P.
  - Hicks, C. S.
  - Hicks, Frank D.
  - Hiden, Robert B.
  - Higbee, David Rathburn
  - Higginbottom, Annie
  - Higgins, Charles H.
  - Higgins, James A.
  - Higgins, Joseph T.
  - Higginson, Eduardo
  - Higginson, Henry L.
  - Highland Country Club
  - Highlands Pine Inn
  - Highman, Walter J.
  - Hilario, Jose S.
  - Hildebrand, W. H., 1923; 2 items
    Includes: Letters concerning publication of his The Cause and Prevention of Cancer.
  - Hilkowich, A. M.
  - Hill, A. Ross
  - Hill, Archibald Vivian, 1922, 1929, 1937; 7 items
    Includes: Letter on his acceptance of Wallace O. Fenn in his laboratory at Manchester, 1922. Letter concerning his Paget Lecture, 1929. Letter about proposed international meeting of Society for the Protection of Science and Learning.
  - Hill, Annette S.
  - Hill, C. C.
  - Hill, Charles
  - Hill, Claude H.
  - Hill, E. C.
  - Hill, Elliot
  - Hill, Elsa Hempl
  - Hill, Mrs. Frank
  - Hill, Frank Ernest
  - Hill, Frederick Trevor
  - Hill, G. T., Jr.
  - Hill, Mrs. George E.
  - Hill, H. W.
  - Hill, Mrs. J. W.
  - Hill, James H. C.
  - Hill, P. S.
  - Hill, Paul A.
  - Hill, Robert C.
  - Hill Ruth
  - Hill, W. H.
  - Hillard, Mary R.
  - Hiller, Alma
  - Hilliard, C. M.
  - Hillkowitz, Philip
  - Hills, Rollin
  - Hilton, Mrs. C.
  - Hilton, Frederick M.
  - Himwich, Harold E.
  - Hince, Hugh S.
  - Hinckley, Frank
  - Hincks, Clarence M.
  - Hindle, E.
  - Hinds, W. E.
  - Hines, Albert B.
  - Hines, Frank T.
  - Hines, Joseph H.
  - Hines, Marion
  - Hines, Walker D.
  - Hinglais H.
  - Hinkle, F. W.
  - Hinkleman, A. J.
  - Hinne, B.
  - Hinsdale, Guy
  - Hinsey, Joseph C.
  - Hintermayer, Rudi H.
  - Hirsch, Dr.
  - Hirsch, Caesar
  - Hirsch, D. I.
  - Hirsch, G. Chr.
  - Hirsch, Harry B.
  - Hirsch, I. S.
  - Hirsch, Joseph H.
  - Hirsch, Julius
  - Hirsch, Nathaniel D. M.
  - Hirschfelder, J. O.
  - Hirschman, R. S.
  - Hirschmann, I. A.
  - Hirschwald, August
  - Hirsh, Harry B.
  - Hirshberg, Leonard K.
  - Hirst, Barton Cooke
  - Hirszfeld, L.
  - Hitchcock, Charles H.
  - Hitchcock, David I.
  - Hitchcock, John S.
  - Hitchcock, Mary E.
  - Hitchens, A. Parker
  - Hitchens, H. J.
  - Hitzrot, James M.
  - Hlava, J.
  - Hoagland, B. W.
  - Hoagland, Hudson, 1932; 3 items
  - Hobbs, Joseph R.
  - Hobson, Dr.
  - Hobson, Alfrieda P.
  - Hobson, F. G.
  - Hoch, August
  - Hoch, Elizabeth
  - Hoch, Theodore A.
  - Hochschild, Kohn and Co.
  - Hockin, May C.
  - Hodes, William A.
  - Hodge, Grant C.
  - Hodge, Thomas L.
  - Hodges, Leigh Mitchell
  - Hodgkin, Everett
  - Hodgkinson, Cecil H., Jr.
  - Hoe, Charles R., Jr., 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1924-1928
    - Folder 2, 1929-1933
  - Hoe, Richard M.
  - Hoeber, Paul B.
  - Hoeber, Rudolf
  - Hoefle, Hedwig
  - Hojer, Axel J.
  - Hoffher, M.
  - Hoffherr, Fred G.
  - Hoffman, Donald Clare
  - Hoffman, Frederick L.
  - Hoffman, George L.
  - Hoffman, J. L.
  - Hoffman, Jacob B.
  - Hoffman, Joseph K.
  - Hoffman, Louis W.
  - Hoffman, R. O.
  - Hoffman, R. V.
  - Hoffman Arms, The
  - Hoffmann, Erich
  - Hoffmann, W. H.
  - Hoffmann-LaRoche Chemical Works
  - Hoffstadt, N. E.
  - Hofmann, Herbert
  - Hofmeister, ?
  - Hofsoos, Emil
  - Hogue, Mary Jane
  - Hoke, Michael
  - Holbrook, C. S.
  - Holcomb, K. C.
  - Holcombe, John Marshall, Jr.
  - Holder, Clara S.
  - Holderman, H. H.
  - Holfelder, Dr.
  - Holladay, Collis H.
  - Hollaender, Alexander
  - Hollan, Leslie J.
  - Holland, John A.
  - Holland, Maurice
  - Holland, W. M.
  - Hollen, Henry
  - Holler, Gottfried
  - Hollerman, J. Fletcher
  - Holliday Bookshop
  - Hollinger, Bernhard
  - Hollingshead, Enoch
  - Hollingsworth, I. Pemberton P.
  - Hollis, Austin W.
  - Hollister, William
  - Holloway, Mary
  - Hollyer, Frederick
  - Holm, Frits
  - Holm, Whitlock and Scarff
  - Holman, W. L.
  - Holmes, Christian R.
  - Holmes, Francis O.
  - Holmes, George F.
  - Holmes, George W.
  - Holmes, Thomas J.
  - Holmes, Spicer
  - Holmquist, C. A.
  - Holohan, Florence
  - Holst, Axel
  - Holst, Peter M.
  - Holt, Henry
  - Holt, Luther Emmett, 2 folders
    Includes: Correspondence concerning John D. Rockefeller's new endowment for RIMR, 1910; about completion of Rockefeller Institute Hospital and arrangements for its formal opening, 1910. Letter from SF to Holt on renewal of Rockefeller grant to fund Ehrlich's work on chemotherapy, 1910. Letter concerning a new head of department for cancer work at RIMR; SF suggests Leo Loeb or Prof. von Dungern of Heidelberg, 4/27/10. Letter on Oswald Avery's acceptance of position of bacteriologist at RIMR Hospital, 1910. Notices of quarterly meetings of Scientific Directors of RIMR. Letter about nature of research at RIMR, especially change of emphasis of research and relationship of workers at institutions supported by Rockefeller funds to those at RIMR, 5/14/19. Letter from SF to Holt on nutrition work of Osborne, Mendel and McCollum; SF questions whether RIMR should become involved in that field of work, 816/19. Arrangements for meeting of Committee of Nutrition of RIMR, Nov. 1919. Notes on a discussion concerning nutrition research, Dec. 1919. General correspondence. Biographical notes on Holt by SF, 1924.
    - Folder 1, 1910-1918
    - Folder 2, 1919-1928
  - Holt, Mrs. W. D.
  - Holt, Winifred
  - Holtegel, C. F.
  - Holt-Harris, John E.
  - Holton, Henry D.
  - Holtz, Louis
  - Holtzendorff, P. W.
  - Holway, John A.
  - Holzager, Theo G.
  - Homan, Robert B.
  - Homen, Ernst Alexander
  - Homer, Annie
  - Homestead Pharmacy
  - Hon, Conrad
  - Honeij, James A.
  - Honnorat, Andre
  - Honolulu Star Bulletin
  - Hoobler, B. Raymond
  - Hood, George E.
  - Hooker, Donald R.
  - Hooker, Sanford B.
  - Hookworm
  - Hooper, Catharine
  - Hooper, Charles W.
  - Hooper, F. H.
  - Hoover, Mr.
  - Hoover, C. F.
  - Hoover, Herbert
  - Hoover, P. D.
  - Hopewell, H. W.
  - Hopewell, R.
  - Hopkins, Frederick D.
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Frederick Gowland
  - Hopkins, Harris H.
  - Hopkins, Harry L.
  - Hopkins, J. H.
  - Hopkins, Joseph Gardner
  - Hopkirk, C. S. M.
  - Hopp, Julius
  - Hoppin, Frances
  - Hoppin, Frederick S.
  - Horan, Mabel
  - Hori, Ichiro B.
  - Horiuchi, Yuji
  - Hornaday, Frank A.
  - Hornaday, William P.
  - Hornaday, William T.
  - Hornby, H. E.
  - Horner, H. H.
  - Horne's Zoological Arena Co.
  - Hornor, Albert A.
  - Hornsby, John A.
  - Horovitz, K.
  - Horowitz, Murray P.
  - Horsfall, J. L.
  - Horton, Byron
  - Horton, C. C.
  - Horton, Mary B.
  - Horvath, A. A.
  - Horwarth, Edmund J.
  - Horwath, Mrs. B. C.
  - Horwood, W. D.
  - Hosain, S. A.
  - Hosie, Henry
  - Hoskins, R. G.
  - Hospital for Joint Diseases
  - Hospital Supply Company
  - Hotchkiss, Robert S.
  - Hotchkiss, Rollin D., 1935; 1 item
  - Hotopp, Marion
  - Houck, U. G.
  - Houda, Emilian O.
  - Hough, M. P. H.
  - Hough, Theodore
  - Houghton, E. M.
  - Houghton, H. H.
  - Houghton, Henry S., 2 folders